Now, I’m going to show you about dealing the cards, we’re going to always start from the left, going to the right player.
So here, this is how it goes.
Let’s put a few hands out, here’s one, another player’s two, another player’s three.
Now I’m going to deal to myself, I’m going to put this card down, to the dealer.
The next card is up, what I do is put it toward the right of the card, why?
Because you can see both cards easily, the numerical value, it’s easy to read for the dealer and the player.
We’ll put the next card up, the next card up, and the dealer’s card up.
Again, dealing goes left to right and this order.
And then I get my last card.
Another way you can do this, just a simple, slight, difference would be this.
Again, dealing up, up, up, dealer card up, up, up, up and in this case, the next card I put is down or called the hole card, and again, slide into the table so nobody can see and put it under.
It’s just a slight difference but you might be able to do it that way too.